

CONTACT ME AT

- House#1, ST#1, Mughal Chowk, Sialkot Road, Gujranwala Punjab, Pakistan
- syeduzair222.sus@gmail.com
- github.com/uzaircs2022
- www.linkedin.com/in/syed-uzair-8954b0193
- www.facebook.com/uzair.gardazi/
- +92 302 222 4500

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •• Python/C++/Java Developer
- • Web Development
- Android Development
- Data Structures
- • Work Management
- • Team Leading

CERTIFICATE RECEIVED

- Python\C++ developer by
 Namal Institute
- Best Team Management by Voice of Namal

SYED UZAIR

COMPUTER SCIENTIST

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a self-motivated person primarily interested in learning new things. I always wanted and enjoy working with a team of professionals as it opens a new door to new learning. I did many projects related to Python\C++ including web development. I was the director of Management of the only Bussiness Society of NAMAL KNOWLEDGE CITY and Currently working as a President of the Media Society. In addition to this, I also worked as a Virtual Assistant at AMAZON where I handle tasks like product hunting, product launching\ranking, and account managing,

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Namal Institute Mianwali

Bachelors in Computer Science | Oct 2018 - Present

- Doing BS honors in Computer Science
- Current CGPA 3.453
- Got A-/A in all core subjects of CS

Aspire College

Faculty of Science | 2016-2018

- Did Fsc Pre-engineering in a well-recognized institute
- Got 80% marks
- Was Head Boy of the class

Projects

- Face Recognition in Artificial Intelligence
- Determination Of live Coordinates of the satellite using data
- Learning Management system (Using Data Base)
- Search Engine (with O(1) Complexity)
- Creation of Artificial Neural Networks
- System Call creation in the Operating system
- Face with Mask/Without_Mask Recognition
- Heuristic Evaluation of a Website
- Bank Management System
- Pakistan aisa Kiun ha? (A python code analyzing strategy to answer different questions)
- Fruits Classification from a data set.
- Snails 1player game with an artificial agent
- Family Structure using Prolog
- Paranoid Game in Scratch
- Tic Tac Toe

WORK EXPERIENCE

President At VON

Voice Of Namal | NOV 2019 - March 2020

• Lead a Media society as a HEAD

Director Management

Idea Club | Nov 2018 - OCT 2019

- Collaborated with different societies of other institutes i.e. LUMS
- Organized a Stock exchange workshop.